

Personal Details



Street **Postal Code** City



Phone nr.



e-mail



LinkedIn GitHub



22-12-1990



Nederlandse

Languages



••••



00000 DE 00000

Skills



Python 00000 Qlik 00000



MS VBA 00000



MS Office 00000 Talend

00000

00000

00000

00000

00000



HTML 00000



CSS

SQL

Dataiku

C++

JavaScript 00000



Django 00000



MongoDB 00000



Mendix 00000



C# 00000



SAP 00000

Mike Bidinger

A true analytical engineer with both data-management and change-management knowledge and experience. Apart from the fact that I already have quite a bit of knowledge, I keep challenging myself and others to broaden my knowledge. My goal is often to realize the best possible reporting and analysis environment for end users. Overseeing the entire process, from the source systems up to and including the analysis, is self-evident. I bring together the functional requirements, organizational interests and technical possibilities within data-driven solutions. This makes me the link between Business and IT and able to understand the question behind the question, to make the translation between customer and technology. In addition, I'm communicatively strong, proactive and I can work independently as well as together within a team.

Work Experience

VDL Nedcar, Born

Feb 2018 – present

BDQS (Launch and Change Control, Supply)

Product-data-management specialist and responsible for the product-data-quality. Managing and developing automation processes for efficiency and quality of product related data (backend). In addition, also responsible for providing the business with accurate information by transforming data into information to enable data-driven decision making (front-end).

VDL Nedcar, Born

Dec 2017 - Feb 2018

Change Controller (Launch and Change Control, Supply)

Responsible for the validation, implementation and processing of product-engineeringchanges. In addition, a hardware/software product-implementation specialist.

VDL Nedcar, Born

Jan 2017 – Dec 2017

SQA Line Complaints E/E (Supplier Quality Assurance)

Production disruption support through product quality issues. When by analysis is determined that the is supplier related, complaint costs to the relevant supplier. In addition, responsible for updating software components as a result of engineering changes to the product(s), as well as providing support to the "Rework and Repair" department with the product defect analysis of software components.

Prodrive Technologies, Son (Science Park Eindhoven)

Aug 2012 – Jan 2017

Work Preparator, Test Engineer (SMD Assembly)

Responsible for the quality checks through visual test equipment and programming as well as optimizing the SMD production processes through problem analysis (quality and efficiency improvements). In addition, responsible as a work preparator to ensure a high quality and efficiency standard to the start of production for the SMD production processes of new products.

Education

Bachelor of Science	e (HBO) -	- Electrical Engineering
Hogeschool Zund	Hearlen	Graduated: Ves / No

2008 - 2012

HAVO – Nature and Technology / Nature and Health

2004 - 2008

Trevianum Scholengroep, Sittard, Graduated: Yes / No

Courses

Qlik Sense Developer	2022
Qlik Sense Front End Developer	2020
Mendix Rapid Developer	2019
Viscom Release Training	2016
Viscom Basic Training	2012